Lose the map. Find your heart.
A Royal Runaway Romance is a tv movie, comedy,
romance film directed by David Weaver.
Princess Amelia of Bundbury travels across America to explore a budding romance
with an artist, only to fall in love with her bodyguard, Grady.
Princess Amelia, played by Philippa Northeast.
Grady Beck, played by Brant Daugherty.
Wes Riverton, played by Andre Anthony.
Ava, played by Sarah-Jane Redmond.
Andreas, played by Vincent Gale.
Camille, played by Khamisa Wilsher.
Philippa Northeast (born 23 September 1994) is an Australian actress, known for her role
as Evelyn MacGuire in the soap opera Home and Away from 2013 until 2017.
After leaving Home and Away, Northeast starred in the 2019 romantic
comedy film Standing Up for Sunny with RJ Mitte.
She also starred in the Hallmark television film A Royal Runaway Romance (2022).
In 2023, Northeast played the recurring role of Lily in
the Australian comedy series In Limbo.
She was also cast as Kay Walters in the second season of The Newsreader, and
joined the supporting cast of Network 10 drama Paper Dolls.
She plays Susie Lawson in the 2024 neo-Western series Territory.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.